Cancerous Fluid Comes Out IMMEDIATELY After PRAYER!!!
HEALING TIME
The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature
and although it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the Glory of God.
Twenty-five year old Mr. Ganiu Sulaimon from Kwara State, Nigeria,
has come to The Synagogue Church of All Nations with an excruciating problem of leg cancer.
He gets up from the seat to show the very place the cancer has developed.
The camera closes in to get a closer shot of the wound.
You can see that the skin of his entire leg has severely deteriorated.
Flaking dead skin; symptoms of the cancerous infection that has enveloped his right leg
This condition has gone beyond the power of nature,
that no medical technology or medicines can solve this man's problem.
It can only be treated, but it cannot be healed.
This problem has become a curse, and who can remove the curse?
It is none other than Jesus Christ
1 Peter 2:24 to 25 says, "He bore our sins in His body on a tree, so that we might die to sins and live for righteousness."
By his wounds, we are healed.
Mr. Ganiu Sulaimon waits in faith at the Synagogue Church of All Nations' prayer line,
believing that Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today, and forever,
and that just an encounter with Him through His servant, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
will bring perfect healing in Jesus' name.
Prophet T.B. Joshua has arrived at the prayer line as an ambassador of Christ,
sending God's appeal through him, that Jesus Christ is the master healer,
and that He heals for the salvation of their souls.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
The pus and poisonous substances that were compressed under the skin,
instantly begins to gush out of his leg, and pours out on the ground.
What is happening to Mr. Sulaimon?
This is beyond human comprehension.
This confirms what Apostle Paul says in 1 Corinthians, chapter 2, verse 4:
"My message and my preaching were not with wise and persuasive words . . . so that your faith might not rest on human wisdom, but on God’s power."
The woman rolling on the ground is Mr. Ganiu Salaimon's mother
jubilating at what Jesus Christ has done for her son.
Mr. Ganiu Salaimon begins to walk in the light of his testimony, testify that the pain has gone.
Hallelujah!
Look at the boy! The boy is now walking; walking majestically.
Shall we put our hands together for the Lord Jesus?
To God be the Glory!
Mr. Ganiu Salaimon is completely healed after receiving prayer from prophet T.B. Joshua in Jesus' name.
Thank you, Jesus.
Mr. Ganiu Salaimon and his mother walk victorious down the prayer line,
giving thanks to Jesus Christ for His healing power and deliverance
Who is like Jesus? Who is like the Lord?
There is absolutely nobody like Jesus Christ.
On the left, we saw Mr. Ganiu Salaimon suffering with an excruciating problem of leg cancer, but on the right,
you can see Mr. Ganiu Salaimon's skin is completely restored
after receiving prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua in Jesus' name.
His leg is now perfectly healthy.
Tapping the area where the leg cancer once was,
Mr. Ganiu Salaimon testifies that he no longer feels any pain.
TESTIMONY TIME
The problem that brought me here today was leg cancer.
I had been to many hospitals, but all to no avail.
I could not walk, stand, or go to the toilet on my own.
I had to be carried to the restroom.
When the pains became unbearable, I lost hope that I would ever walk again.
When I came to The S.C.O.A.N, Prophet T.B. Joshua stretched his hand towards my leg and prayed for me.
He then told me to rise up.
Immediately, it burst open and all the cancerous substances started gushing out of my leg.
Mr. Ganiu Salaimon rolls up his trousers and testifies that Jesus Christ has set him free.
He once again taps the area where the leg cancer formerly was,
Mr. Ganiu Salaimon: There is no pain; I am free now.
Demonstrating that he is healed.
He says there is no more pain.
This is a confirmation that the Gospel of Jesus Christ is indeed the power of God
for the salvation of everyone who believes. Romans 1:6.